Anne, listen to this!
I'm advancing to the next grade!
I made it to the second year!
That is cause to celebrate.
Yeah!
Now Mother won't disown me!
Thank goodness!
I need to be careful, though.
In the game, Catarina is judged
for her evil deeds just before Nicol
and the other second-years
have their graduation party,
and she meets her doom in the end...
Oh, sorry! I was talking to myself.
It's all right. I'm used to it.
I'm going to tell everyone else the news!
Goodbye, then.
Oh! I forgot to mention something!
I made it to my second year
because I had you!
Thank you!
I... haven't done anything...
You've stayed by my side! That's what counts!
HameFura, I Reincarnated
into an
Otome Game
as a
Villainess
with only
destruction flags···
aimaina I my me datte guruguru mazetara
If you mix it round and round it becomes unclear
akogare no kyuu tenkai ni niau kamo ne
With an unexpected development, maybe it will look good
ren ai nara iza morase
If it's love, express it now
tobikiri no dessert
with wonderful desserts
amazuppai cho misu wa oyurushi asobase
An addictive sweet and sour mix, I'm sorry to have fun
mawaru uruwashiki koi moyou
Love is a spiral pattern that spins on and on
chotto souzou naname you he massugu susume
I need to stop and think before moving forward
otome no route wa hitotsu janai
A maiden's route is not just one!
hatto suru lucky na ima ni gokigen you
My heart feels surprisingly lucky now
itsudatte maemukina desu
And so I will remain optimistic
ai mo kawarazu ni touhonseisou kou kando wo agete
If you want to win the game of love, you have to risk it all
kiyoku tadashiku utsukushiku are to wa yoku itta monda na
It's a pure, intense and beautiful feeling, so fight for it
kitto warui happy na mirai ni gokigen you
I still don't know if my ending will be happy or not
itsu datte maemukina desu
But I will remain optimistic
Episode 9
Things Got Crazy at a Slumber Party...
Congratulations, Sister.
We must do something to celebrate!
Catarina-sama is terribly troublesome,
but she's very popular within certain circles.
for instance, with Geordo Stuart-sama,
Catarina-sama is completely oblivious to his feelings.
She even suggested breaking off their engagement once.
My wound has healed, so you don't have to take responsibility anymore.
You can break off the engagement.
The wound hasn't healed.
I will never break off our engagement.
What? But it should be healed...
I've checked in the mirror so many times.
Right, Anne?
You were mistaken.
The scar is most definitely still there.
Well, don't you agree with me?
Frankly, that scared me so much
I think it reduced a few years off my life.
You know, I'm hopeless with written exams,
Keith-sama secretly has feelings for Catarina-sama.
but practical exams...
But because Catarina-sama is so dense,
she has no idea how he feels.
Oh, he's just too hot!
I can't bring myself to approach him!
I've been hearing that you're unbelievably hot.
You might end up with a girlfriend in no time.
It doesn't matter if people call me hot.
If the person I want to see it doesn't,
then what's the point?
I truly had to sympathize him.
My sister is not fit to be a prince's consort!
Opposed!!
Catarina is not fit to be a prince's consort!!
And now,
Opposed!!
Catarina is not fit to be a prince's consort!!
he's doing everything in his power to break up
Catarina-sama and Geordo-sama's engagement.
Opposed!!
Catarina is not fit to be a prince's consort!!
Catarina is not fit to be a prince's consort!
Opposed!!
Catarina is not fit to be a prince's consort!!
Not fit!
Opposed!!
Catarina is not fit to be a prince's consort!!
And Alan Stuart-sama's feelings
toward Catarina-sama are also...
Why do I have to play for a bunch of poorly-raised potatoes?
I heard music is good for vegetables, too!
Please!
Oh, fine...
Thank you very much, Alan-sama!
But sadly, Alan-sama still seems
to be unaware of his own feelings.
Mary Hunt-sama also loves Catarina-sama.
In fact, she's plotted quite a terrifying plan.
I'm not fit for a position so important as a prince's consort.
If you're unfit, then it's even more impossible for me.
I have no idea what I'm meant to do.
Then let's both cancel our engagements
and flee to somewhere far away!
It would be nice to live near the sea!
Yes!
This island has boats departing
for the city three times a day.
We wouldn't have any difficulty getting by!
You're such a nice girl, Mary.
But because Catarina-sama is so dense,
she has no idea that Mary-sama is actually serious.
Nicol Ascart-sama seems to have
feelings for Catarina-sama, as well.
He rarely speaks first to anyone
or changes his expression,
but in front of Catarina-sama, even Nicol-sama...
shows a smile that looks truly happy.
And Sophia Ascart-sama also loves Catarina-sama.
Sophia-sama noticed how Nicol-sama,
her brother, felt before anyone else,
and she's been trying her hardest
to get Catarina-sama to realize it...
My brother is just so kind!
My brother is just so brave!
My brother is just so adorable!
Adorable?
Yes!
You're really attached to your brother, aren't you?
But unfortunately, the message isn't coming through at all.
And Maria Campbell-sama also loves Catarina-sama.
Catarina-sama, please eat these.
Thank you!
Which is why I say that,
within certain circles, Catarina-sama is quite popular.
What is it about Catarina-sama
that draws people to her?
In truth, I know the answer to that.
Then we'll see you again this evening.
Yes, I look forward to it.
Is something happening this evening?
We're all having pajama party.
All of you? A pajama party?
What exactly do you do at a pajama party?
We all get together in our pajamas,
eating delicious snacks,
and spend time chatting together.
That sounds delightful.
Oh, I know!
Why don't you boys have a boys-only party?
What are you talking about, Sister?
That's never going to happen.
Aw, Keith, why not?
A boys-only party would be lovely!
You can spend the whole night talking about boy stuff!
No, that wouldn't be the least bit lovely.
I don't even know what we'd talk about all night.
Nicol-sama, you agree with me, right?
The whole night... talking about boy stuff?
Wait, are you serious, Nicol-sama?
I think it sounds fun.
What?!
You, too, Alan-sama?!
We still have time.
Wait, you two...
Just the boys... talking all night?
Catarina-sama! What is all this?
They're my pajamas for the party tonight.
I just can't decide which ones to wear.
I'm thinking of wearing these
What do you think?
You look lovely, but aren't there any other options?
Really?
Then...
How about these? They light up in the dark!
I think, perhaps, something a bit more subdued...
Aw!
It's not a girls-only party without love talk!
Does anyone here have a sweetheart?
Yeah, I guess none of us do...
All right!
There's still no relationship progress between
Maria and the conquerable characters!
Which means there can't be any doom flags triggered yet!
That reminded me that there's
something I wanted to ask all of you.
If you were seeing someone,
what would you want to do with them?
Huh?
I'm not sure...
Catarina-sama, please give us your answer!
Um, let me think...
I guess I'd want to make them a meal
from the vegetables I raised.
Okay, next! What about you, Maria?
Um... I...
I'd want to make sweets for them.
I'm learning how to cook, too,
so when I get good at it, I'd want to cook for them.
Your cooking would be amazing, Maria!
I want to taste-test it!
Yes, of course!
What about you, Mary-sama?
I'd want to eat meals with them, bathe with them...
B-Bathe?
And we could comb each other's hair...
Oh, and we could style each other's hair...
And we could trade dresses!
Huh?
You wouldn't trade dresses with a boy, would you?
What? Does the partner have to be a boy?
Well, I just assumed it would be...
Huh?
In that case, I can't think of anything.
I'm happier when I'm with you, Catarina-sama.
All right, Sophia-sama, you're last.
My wishes are all ordinary things.
Like visiting bookstores together...
Uh-huh!
And fighting together for the good of our country,
freeing their heart from the darkness lurking within it,
undoing the curse placed on them by an evil witch,
searching for the legendary ring so
we can explore the world of the gods,
These are ordinary?
singing for the people who are fighting for a revolution...
Um, Catarina-sama, is this...
Even though they were abducted as a child
Yeah... This all happened in a romance novel.
and taken in by a family of traveling performers...
I borrowed it from her and read it a while ago.
By the way, Anne, has there been
any talk of marriage for you?
Perhaps it's already been
decided who your partner will be?
Really? What are they like?
Please tell us!
There is no such person.
I have no desire to get married, anyway.
What?
You don't?
Why not?
Well...
I know!
I have a question for all of you, too!
If you could be reborn, what would you want to be?
Reborn?!
That happens in lots of romance novels, too!
I'd want to be a princess
in a forbidden relationship with a knight!
Maybe a female knight who dresses as a man,
I'd have to say a man of higher
status than Prince Geordo.
or a nun who's fled from her convent,
Let's see... I think...
or a fairy who falls in love with a human,
or a legendary holy sword...
Anne, it's late. Go get some rest.
Very well. I will take my leave, then.
Goodnight.
Goodnight!
I was born to Baron Shelley and one of his maids.
I did exactly as my mother wished,
behaving meekly and submissively
so that the baron would like me.
I was convinced that I was happy with that life.
However...
When I was fifteen years old,
my mother died in a fire.
With that scar,
you're of no use to me as a political marriage pawn.
I have no further need of you. Leave this house.
The baron never had any interest in me at all.
I was only a tool...
someone he didn't need anymore.
Then I took a job as a maid in the home
of Duke Claes, a distant relative.
Catarina-sama was a pampered child,
making her very selfish and arrogant.
I only tried to be a useful tool for my master,
as I had been to the baron.
I remained meek and submissive,
with no will of my own.
But after the events of one day, Catarina-sama changed.
She was far from the typical well-bred lady.
I had no idea how I should interact with her,
but before I knew it, I had learned
to act of my own will and speak my own mind.
Around Catarina-sama, who was cheerful,
energetic, and treated everyone equally,
I could no longer be just a tool.
The first birthday present I ever received...
Catarina-sama accepted and loved me for who I was.
Then, just when I began to wish
that I could spend the rest of my life here...
Your wedding date has been set.
I will be sending for you. Be ready.
I found you a partner who's benevolent enough to take you,
even though you're damaged goods.
Why are you still standing there?! Get ready at once!
You're Anne's father, yes?
My name is Catarina Claes.
Y-Yes...
I have a favor to ask.
Please reconsider making Anne get married!
I need Anne!
I want her by my side!
You can't take her from me!
Let me tell you just how important
and necessary Anne is to me!
First, in the mornings,
she always wakes me up when I sleep too late
and fixes my hair for me!
No, wait! I need to go back ever further!
Um... I'm a restless sleeper,
so I always kick my blanket off,
but Anne always gets up at least once per night
to fix my blanket for me!
Please let Anne stay with me!
Please!
I would like...
to decline this marriage offer.
What?!
I will not be ordered around by you, Father.
What did you say?! Watch your tongue!
Pardon me.
Baron...
I would like to speak with you for a moment.
Catarina-sama made me into the person named Anne Shelley.
I will follow her wherever she goes.
By Catarina-sama's side is where I am truly happy.
Geordo-sama.
A letter has arrived for you.
It's from Catarina?
How unusual for her to take the trouble to write.
Dear Geordo Stuart-sama,
Please come to the terrace
in the garden behind the school.
I'll be waiting for you.
Catarina Claes.
The normal Catarina wouldn't choose
such an elegant, showy card...
And asking me to come
to a place that's usually deserted...
Could this be...
Geordo-sama...
I've finally realized how I feel.
You are the one I...
No, wait. Calm down.
This is Catarina we're talking about.
It couldn't be something that amorous.
It must be something else.
It's the latest model of toy snake!
Still, as her fiancé,
I can't decline this invitation.
Maybe I should prepare a gift to give her.
Considering the occasion,
it should be the thing that would make her happiest...
The shears I always use haven't
been cutting as well, as of late.
Gardening shears...
But...
That couldn't possibly be any less romantic.
It doesn't seem like a gift
that a prince should give his fiancée.
Still, I have confidence
that she'll like it far more than any
gaudy, extravagant ornament.
I haven't been watching her from right
by her side all these years for nothing.
Since that's settled, I must arrange her gift right away!
I'll have it engraved with her name,
put it in a fine case, and...
What's gotten into Geordo-sama?
How unusual. He's absolutely giddy.
Geordo-sama...
What are all of you doing here?
You sent them to everyone, Catarina?!
Hey!
Thanks for coming, everyone!
Welcome to my grand harvest day!
Harvest day?
A
Geordo
I had work outfits made for all of you!
A
Geordo
Mary
Alan
A
Geordo
Mary
Alan
A
Geordo
Mary
Alan
A
Geordo
Mary
Alan
A
Geordo
Mary
Alan
A
Geordo
Mary
Maria
Alan
Nicol
A
Geordo
Mary
Maria
Alan
Nicol
Mary
Maria
Alan
Nicol
A
Geordo
Mary
Maria
Alan
Nicol
A
Geordo
Mary
Maria
Alan
Nicol
Mary
Maria
Alan
Nicol
A
Geordo
Mary
Maria
Alan
Nicol
Mary
Maria
Alan
Nicol
Mary
Maria
Alan
Nicol
A
Geordo
Please use them!
That's what this is about?
Everyone!
You look fantastic!
Catarina.
This is for you.
Please use it if you like.
Thank you very much, Geordo-sama!
You're welcome.
I'm happy just to see you smile like th—
Everyone, thank you for all the beautiful shears!
Well... I suppose I should have seen this coming...
kokoro ga tsukiru made moyase
My heart yearns for you so much
kantan ni clear dekiru
I thought it was easy to clear
koi wa game sou omotteta
To win at this love game
gururi madowasete hikiyosete
I'm spinning around and pulling you in
otosu shudai wo narabuke wo
Following along in my footsteps
naze kimi dakara igai
Why are you so captivating?
dono route erabeba saita nano ka
Which route will be the best choice?
kotae wa mienai
I can't find the answer
Bad End no unmei demo boku no mono ni nareba ii
Even if fate leads me to a "Bad End", it's fine
sou saa douse hametsu suru no nara kimi to
You're the one I want in my life
zettai ni zetsumei shinai aida to chikaukara
My love for you will never change
ubai saa nareru kakugo
Prepare to be conquered
mubou mi de muteki nayosashisa mudai makichirasu mae ni
You make me feel invincible, imprudent and happy at the same time
sono chisen wo hitorijime shitte miseru
I want to find out more about you
donna kodoku mo itami mo
No matter how much the pain is
kimi goto uketomeru
I will carry it for you
machi ukeru zetsubou mo nozomu tokoro
Even if despair awaits me, I'll take it on
The seasons have passed,
and autumn is now giving way to winter.
It appears I've avoided setting any of my doom flags thus far.
And then it happened out of nowhere...
Catarina Claes,
we are going to expose all of the evil
deeds you have committed, here and now!
Evil deeds? Me?